{
  "name": "Rounding Off Numbers",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Round the following number to nearest 10:\n63",
      "answers": ["60"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the following number to nearest 10:\n7,552",
      "answers": ["7,550"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the following number to nearest 10:\n9,527",
      "answers": ["9,530"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the following number to nearest 100:\n32,589",
      "answers": ["32,600"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the following number to nearest 100:\n63,214",
      "answers": ["63,200"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the following number to nearest 100:\n4,78,965",
      "answers": ["4,79,000"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the following number to nearest 1000:\n63,254",
      "answers": ["63,000"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Round the following number to nearest 1000:\n7,41,236",
      "answers": ["7,41,000"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "The human body has 206 bones. Can it be rounded off to the nearest 100?\nAnswer Yes or No.",
      "answers": ["YES"],
      "keyboard": "yes_no",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "School begins at 8 am. Can it be rounded off to the nearest 10?\nAnswer Yes or No.",
      "answers": ["YES"],
      "keyboard": "yes_no",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "25 children were sent to the circus. Can it be rounded off to the nearest 10?\nAnswer Yes or No.",
      "answers": ["YES"],
      "keyboard": "yes_no",
      "timeout": 180
    }
  ]
}